This episode of Dissect is presented by
Amazon Prime. The holidays hit fast. One
moment you're planning, the next
everything's out of sync. Luckily, Prime
helps you catch the rhythm with fast,
free delivery that gets it there just in
time. Prime's fast shipping is always
there for you during the holidays,
especially when it's last minute and it
just can't wait. Hosting essentials or
the gift that hits the right note, it's
on Prime. Head to amazon.com/prime
to shop now.
I'm going to go with worst song. Okay.
And I'm sorry I had to do it to him.
He's a legend. Okay.
Wow. Is the one of the worst is the
worst song of the 21st century. When
that song comes on, I I'm in a bad mood
now.
It's a kid song. It's on a kid It's a
kids movie. Like [__] the kids.
Welcome everyone to a special episode of
Dissect. I'm your host Cole Kushner and
today we are doing a very special
year-end 21st century song draft with
the LWS crew. Charles is in the
building. What's up?
>> How you doing, my man?
IRL? Uh it's it's always a joy to see
you. But what I want to say, I want to
say a special shout-out because this is
the first time we're reuniting after the
season, you know, and people gave us
love. Like we were very nervous behind
the scenes. We're like, we're changing
it up a little bit. We're doing
something different.
The I felt it. I felt also some of the
hate, but that's cool, too. You got to
roll with the punches. After the season,
how do you feel like we did with with
some time distance?
>> I feel like actually the yeah, the
general reception was great. This is
kind of like a sequel to our 21st So
people that aren't familiar, we did a
eight-episode series trying to to figure
out what the best album of the 21st
century so far. Today we're going to do
a 21st century song draft.
And we also have Justin Sales, producer
Justin will be joining us for the draft.
How you doing, Justin? I'm doing okay,
but I'm struggling to figure out where
this love came from because anytime
somebody's like, "Hey, check what
they're saying about you in the YouTube
comments." I'm like, "Why you going to
send that to me, right? Why you going to
Here's the thing, sometimes I'll be
scrolling through the YouTube comments
and I'm like,
"Damn, they cooked me on this one."
Yeah. I'm like, "Shit." Real recognize
real.
But what I'm just happy about is I'm not
here to be the tiebreaker this time.
>> Oh, yeah, yeah.
>> here to mess this up on my own.
Okay. Should we reveal the categories
for today's draft?
>> Yes. Okay. So we're going to draft from
six categories. The categories are
number one hit song, so had to chart on
the Billboard 200 number one for at
least one week, best song/most important
song, kind of kind of however you want
to take that, worst song, Yep, that's
easy. I'm going to get I'm getting spicy
on this one. Okay. I Okay, yeah, I do
have a trigger song that uh might
trigger you, Charles, specifically.
One-hit wonder,
which is I actually very excited about,
>> Same.
and personal favorite. So it's kind of a
wild card, pick whatever whatever you
want, personal favorite. So
to draft order, Justin is going to spin
a digital wheel. This is the instrument
that has helped so many Ringer drafts.
It is wheelofnames.com.
I'm going to I have our names all pulled
up in this.
And okay.
Do you have a draft order preference? Do
you like going first?
I either like going first or I like
going last. Okay.
>> You want to get the turn, right? Cuz we
do the snake draft style, right? You
know, you get first pick, second pick,
third pick, but then third pick goes
first at the top of the next round. So
you want to get the corner.
And
All right. So
Oh, wow. This is crazy.
Uh
It came up right on the line of me and
Charles. But the computer is telling me
the the computer that I just praised, I
never said anything bad about the
computers. I want to go on the record as
saying that I'm the winner and I get the
first pick. Okay. Okay.
And pick number two,
Charles, you're not going to like this.
This is you.
It's fine. You know what? It's I've I've
I've had to come back from worse than
this. You know what I'm saying? I'm
fine.
>> I'm kind of nervous though. I got third.
I mean, it's good, but okay.
All right, first pick in the 21st
century song draft. So just to make it
clear, these are songs from the year
2000 to 2020.
>> So we are counting the year 2000, right?
>> Yes. I I thought we were.
>> Yeah. All right.
Oh, yeah. Even though technically, so we
don't get the comment, the 21st century
starts in 2001, but only nerds say that.
>> Only nerds say that. Okay. So I have the
first pick. Yep.
>> I'm going to go with the number one song
and I'm not going to go nostalgic. I'm
going to stick with the spirit of
Dissect and I'm going to go Not Like Us.
>> [__] you, dude. [__] you. This is crazy.
They not like us. They not like us. This
is kind of
Actually, this is bad. We should start
over. Drafting Not Like Us is you should
get you disqualified. Why? Early? This
early? Is like crazy like Well, Justin
knows his audience and he's playing the
game already. I forgot how competitive
you two are. This is
This is ugly.
I'm going with Not Like Us.
>> For the number one hit, too?
>> For number one hit.
>> best moment?
>> Not even best moment. I got other stuff
for best moment. I'm going number one
hit. And I'm picking Not Like Us. Well,
okay.
First of all, I want to say this about
number one song.
Shocked that a lot of songs didn't hit
number one, right? Like Get Lucky, not
number one. Even stuff like Britney
Spears' Toxic, not number one. A lot of
songs that were everywhere that you
thought would have did not hit number
one.
>> Yeah.
I
went over the list of number one singles
again and again and again. And I just I
there were three songs, four songs that
I think I would have been five top that
I would have been really comfortable
with, but knowing my audience, knowing
where we are,
going Not Like Us. I hate this one. You
don't got to We don't got to put too
much on that. We just all know how I
feel about it. It shouldn't be allowed.
Um it's it's cowardly, but it's my pick
now.
So I'm getting spicy. [__] it, you know?
I'm I'm super excited. I'm going best
most important song. Okay.
And I'm picking um
I'm picking a cursed object, but I'm
picking it for a reason because I feel
like not only did this song break my
brain and it's one of my favorite songs
of the 21st century, I think it
represents arguably the most important,
controversial, um
idiotic artist of the 21st century. I'm
going Kanye West Runaway, best song.
This is a cursed episode, so what are we
doing? But I was like, all right, you
guys
I want to win the draft. I was thinking
about what Kanye song would like
I was like, do I pick a Kanye song? If
I'm going to pick one, why would I pick
it? And I think Runaway is the moment
where I'm like everything shifts, not
only in the 21st century, but everything
shifts in popular music, where I'm like,
I think Kanye realized that to your
point earlier, we're going to know way
too much about artists and it's not
actually like we're getting to the point
where the currency
is being an [__] And the currency is
just getting as much attention as you
want. And and blowing everything up and
appealing to critics and Twitter and
online fodder and blogs. And when I go
back and I think about Runaway, I'm just
like, okay, it's not the biggest song of
the 21st century,
but I could play it for an It's the
thing we always say. I could play it for
an alien, they'd be like,
"Who is this guy? Wait, who's Pusha T?
Wait, why is there a vocoder outro?"
>> Yeah, you can tell the story of No, I
mean, it is actually the perfect song to
immortalize Kanye West. To rep I mean,
it have a toast for the douchebags. It
showcases musical genius. It gives you a
window into his personality.
The whole entire outro being this
beautiful instrumental that no one else
has ever done shows you the musical
innovation that he brought to the 21st
century. So it is kind of a perfect song
if you're going to try to to represent
Kanye West in the 21st century,
but it's also [__] pick two.
I know it's strategy cuz you you're
trying to get the big songs. I I get the
strategy here, but
>> [__] it. I'm Here's the thing, I've I've
been at this place too long. I didn't
come here to play fair. I'm in the
middle position. Like I got I got a
pathway to victory. What are you doing,
Cole? Cole, but like what's your issue
with picking Not Like Us and and
Runaway? Two songs that you've covered a
lot
>> Yes. It's just too much It's just too
early and
>> Too early? Two Oh, wait, are you just
mad cuz you couldn't pick them? Yes.
>> Exactly.
Welcome to the Ringer, bro. We drafted.
And it's also a little like on the nose,
but I get the strategy in terms of like
this podcast, right? We've talked about
these songs a lot. It's going to get
more interesting as we go on, I think,
but
>> I would have picked Runaway for best
moment.
>> That's It was number one on my best
>> one on my best moment, too.
Uh and we should just cover that
briefly. If for anyone that doesn't
know, the VMAs
Runaway
>> performance, yes.
>> debut performance of Runaway being this
cultural moment at a critical time in
his life and I think his career goes
totally different if that moment goes
differently. And the 21st century of
music certainly goes way differently if
Kanye's never able to recover from that
moment. So Exactly. And I think
everybody has been
I think him running up on stage for
Taylor Swift, everything that happened
after, him going back to the VMAs,
very weirdly gave artists a template for
the shenanigans that they would have to
pull, where it's like
I do think that there is a clear line
between like Pusha T showing up on
stage, you know, and Pusha T dissing
Drake and Not Like Us and just in terms
of just like, yeah, everybody realized
the spectacle had to keep getting bigger
and bigger and bigger and bigger.
>> Right. Yeah.
Okay, so pick number three for me.
This is interesting cuz the two I mean I
was playing the same strategy cuz if I
got the first pick I was going to pick a
Kendrick song and if I got the second
pick I was going to pick Runaway. So
Let me see what other ones that you guys
might pick. I think
>> Oh, we're in his head already Charles.
>> Yeah, man. This is The lights are too
bright Cole. Well, I'm not competitive
you guys. Like I
You guys bring this this toxic
environment in my in my pure podcast and
then I got to play along here. So okay.
So
I Okay, [__] it. I'm going to make
things interesting. I'm going to go with
my number one hit.
Oh, you know what?
Oh, [__] This is even tough too.
Could I Could I lay out two two options
for you just just to make it
interesting? Is there a chance that
one of the options gets picked for
something else if not are you going to
spoil a future pick?
>> I guess I'm only in competition with
Charles with this pick.
>> Okay. Then I don't know.
>> Because you already did your number one.
>> Okay.
How big of a Carly Rae Jepsen fan are
you?
Uh you can have that. Okay.
>> that.
>> that's part of my strategy cuz my second
one
Call Me Maybe?
Fine. It's a fine song. I like it. I
like it. It's There's better pop songs.
It's It's
>> Call Me Maybe
Okay, I'm just going to do it.
No, you know what? No, I'm not going to
do it.
Cuz I I might need that. See, [__] you
guys.
>> it's too early to be
No, you're I'm thinking I'm thinking
ahead. I'm trying to think ahead. I'm
going to go Irreplaceable by Beyoncé.
All right. Interesting.
>> Interesting. I thought you'd be stoked.
Not even on my board.
Really? Not even on my board.
>> left to the left?
There's better Beyoncé songs. At number
one?
Okay, maybe I have a personal place in
my heart for this song and Wait, what
Did it Did it touch you at a at a
certain time in life? Like what like
what were you going on when when
Irreplaceable was out? What were you
going through? It was the anomaly cuz
this is 2007. In Rainbows comes out in
2007. This is the time of Justice and
Killers. This is a very pivotal time in
my musical life. Like
you know, might be the prime of my
musical life in terms of like me coming
of age and everything.
But this song in particular I remember
was my most played song on iTunes in
2007 despite despite all those other
albums.
>> being serious? I'm being serious. I
[__] love this song.
>> about me. It's so good. What? Did you
guys know that Ne-Yo wrote this song and
it was supposed to be a country a
country song first? I did not know this
until I researched this episode, but
Cole. I thought you'd be I thought you'd
have my back on this pick.
>> No, no, I like it. It just wasn't on my
board. Here's the thing. Before Ne-Yo
got We're going to have to say this
about like half the artists. BEFORE
NE-YO GOT PROBLEMATIC
THERE WAS I'LL BE HONEST.
THERE WAS one list. I think it was a
Pitchfork list and I was scrolling down
and Ignition remix was very high.
>> I had the same thing and I was like,
huh, there's there's an alternate
universe where we are drafting that and
thank god we don't live in that
universe.
Yeah, I was just like there were a
couple artists on it and I was like, oh,
okay. Yeah, different time. Is this a
crazy pick Justin?
Am I already regretting it? I Am I not
good at drafting? [__] No, no, dude.
You're doing good. I had another Beyoncé
song potentially listed as my number one
pick and it wasn't this. Okay.
All right.
Shout out Call Me Maybe though. Yeah.
What What's your What's your You got
>> number Oh, okay. I'm number I'm number
three. Okay. You can pick Call Me Maybe
for best song if you'd like. No,
no, thank you.
I don't think you guys will pick this,
but I'm just going to do me at this
point. I'm going to go with my one-hit
wonder. Okay.
I'm going to go with the best song
Future never wrote.
I'm going to go with Future's AI
generated artist and single.
You know You know where I'm going with
this? I do. I'm going Desiigner's Panda.
>> Wow.
Just a great song.
When's the last Okay, let me just let me
just play you guys a snippet. When's the
last time you guys Did you listen to
this song in preparation?
>> way more than you think I would listen
to.
I mean it's it's a kind of a perfect
song. It's not only a perfect song. Can
I pitch you on something?
>> Okay.
We all went to the Vista to see one
battle after another. Great experience.
In that Sheck Wes Mo Bamba. Yo. Oh. If
there was Yeah, that was GOING TO BE MY
ONE-HIT WONDER. OH, HERE'S THE THING
CHARLES. I'M NOT PICKING IT. I'M JUST
SAYING AND IF YOU WERE GOING to replace
that song in the movie Oh, with another
>> it would be just as Can you imagine if
you were sitting in a
theater and a panda just comes out?
I I I have other one-hit wonders, but
I'm you can't spoil it. All right, you
know what?
Now I'm going to
take Justin's song away from him and I'm
going to pick him one-hit wonder. Just
kidding.
It's not part of my stra- strategy.
All right, I got You know what? I'm
going to go with worst song.
And I'm sorry I have to do it to him.
He's a legend. Okay. He's an OG. He
showed us this year. He produced one of
the best albums this year. Oh, no.
Pharrell song?
Happy by Pharrell Williams is the one of
the worst is the worst song of the 21st
century.
What? When that song comes on, I I'm in
a bad mood now.
Get like Y'all don't Y'all hear me
though when you
>> so Charles. When you
Cuz I'm happy. I'm like, [__] SHUT
I HATE THAT SONG.
It's right. It's like literally just
Happy and You Know It Clap Your Hands
just updated for the 20 It's It's really
truly
>> It's a kid song. It's on a It's a kids
movie. Like [__] the kids.
No, like here's the thing. Have you
watched that video recently where Tyler,
the Creator, and Earl the Sweatshirt are
like snapping in the street? I'm like,
nah, bro. Get this at I thought you
would be more supportive. You like
Happy? Yeah, who doesn't like Happy? All
right, man. Is it because it was
overplayed?
It was never fire. Honestly, if we
wanted to get really cursed, I was going
to pick another
another song, Blurred Lines.
Blurred Lines is not the worst song, but
it's the most cursed
>> It's the We should have had a most
cursed category cuz
cuz once again, I saw one of them lists
Blurred Lines was on there. I was like,
Yeah, bad song. Bad song, cursed song. I
just just I never actually liked that
song.
>> That's I was looking at some I can't
remember exactly where it was. It was
like in the top five of the century in
terms of of selling. Just kind of crazy.
>> It's It's like for a pop song it's fine.
>> It's fine. It's fine. It's got the the
Marvin Gaye obviously, but you know, you
have the lawsuit. You got You got T.I.
You got the like when you actually start
to look at the lyrics, it's just a very
cursed song.
But yes, I'm Like I said, I'm going with
Happy. I'm sorry Pharrell. You were an
OG. I'm glad everybody likes this. This
is just a It's like such a Charles the
Cynic pick. The [__] song that's
supposed to make that makes you feel
warm and is related to children and like
purity and happiness is the one of your
worst song. Yep. Nah, this is actually
yeah.
We are We are our truest selves on this
draft. All right, Justin, where you
Where are you going?
>> I'm I'm also going to stick in in worst
song and I Maybe I don't need to because
uh
there were just so many options, but I
just want to get it out of the way.
Um and
I'm happy to run through all these Like
I had Tyga songs on here. I had several
M&M songs listed,
If you picked Rack City, I was I I might
fight you.
I No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no. Rack City's great. No, no, no,
no. I'm not I'm not picking Tyga. I'm
saying my list was very long. We can run
through it later.
I'm going with the actual worst song of
the century and it's also a number one
hit was Rude by Magic.
Yeah.
Do I think people will remember just me
saying it, but it's the you know,
Why you want to be Why you got to be so
rude? I'm going to marry that girl. That
[__] That white boy reggae.
The like
>> The white boy reggae, yeah. It is
such a terrible song. I know nothing
about this group. They're also a one-hit
wonder. It's It's crazy. It's the worst
song. It's a one-hit wonder. It's number
one. I know nothing about this group,
but it is That was a It was a number one
song. I guess that makes sense.
We get negative. I like this. This is a
We get real real negative. Wait. You
know what?
What? I said I got the next pick. Okay.
And I'm actually I'm going to bring us
back to the light. Okay.
I'm going to do Pharrell solid and I'm
going to pick my best song. Oh, wow.
Okay.
I'm going to do Grinding by Clipse.
Inspired choice, sir. This is
Justin's playing a certain game. He
Here's the
I don't even think he's picking his
heart. He's just literally just trying
to
ingratiate himself to the fan base. And
I find it disgusting.
Well, more on that later. However, I
mean, look, you
this song I think only gets better with
age, right? Like I think in the moment
it it really hit, but I don't know.
We're recording this a little bit before
this episode is going to come out, but
Cole and I were in a car with with
friend of the show Logan Murdock last
night and the song came on and it's just
like you know
just everything about the song. Do you
guys like the Pharrell intro?
What for grinding? Yeah, I I I've
learned that some people don't.
>> Wait, which is crazy. Wait, who doesn't?
Name them, shame them. I like I never
actually knew that that was like an
opinion that you could have.
That's racist. Right, it's crazy.
Yeah, it's iconic at this point.
>> Exactly, I the song wouldn't be what it
is without it. Damn, grinding [__] I
like the symbolic aspect of it, too.
It's like Pharrell introducing the world
to these
duo, it's it's perfect.
>> And you know what, I'm making things
right with Pharrell, so if he's
listening to the show like shoutout
Pharrell like I I love Pharrell like
there's other Pharrell songs that I
could have picked in other areas. It's
just like hey yo, it had to when I was
going through the worst songs of the
decade, I was like yo, it had to be him.
I'm sorry, but I love that we bringing
we giving like Pharrell and the Neptunes
some love. Shoutout grinding and the
clips.
>> Shoutout Chad. Shoutout Chad Hugo. Yeah.
Shoutout Chad Hugo. Like honestly
We I'm not going to get too spicy. It's
the clips here. I'm not going to get too
spicy. Shoutout shoutout Chad. Okay,
damn.
Where do I want to go now?
I need a number one song.
>> your worst song and you had your best
song.
>> Best song.
Ooh, okay. You know what?
And one hit no. I'm going to go in one
hit wonder
What's on your short list before you
reveal your
I'm not going to reveal it. Well,
actually Vanessa Carlton's A Thousand
Miles was on my short list.
>> That's a great one. That is a great one.
Rappers love that song, too. Who Let the
Dogs Out Baha Men. That's a curse song.
>> That could have been a worst song.
You know, if we wanted to just if I
wanted the real spirit, what I think the
actual like when we think of what a
number one hit song is like like one hit
wonder I mean
Old Town Road Lil Nas X is like actually
like Is that a one hit is he a one hit
wonder? I I think he had other hits.
Yeah. But I'm like if I ask you to name
them, could you? No, yeah.
This is this is a question. This is a
philosophical question. How do you guys
define one hit wonder? Because there's a
whole different like list of
Yeah, cuz I was trying to think is like
Call Me Maybe one hit wonder, but I
don't think so because she's had she's
never obviously reached that height
again, but she's had a pretty
like she has a core audience and really
respected artist since then, but it's
kind of on the it's on the border of it,
but I think Rude is kind of like the
perfect like example of a one cuz it's
like you comes out of nowhere. Yeah,
they they huge never heard from again.
>> Yeah, exactly. All right, that's why
that's why I'm not going to pick Lil Nas
X. I'm going to go with my heart.
I thought this was the greatest song in
the world.
When it dropped, I would watch MTV2
religiously.
I knew all the words. It hit the the
suburbs like an atomic bomb. I'm going
Ridin' Dirty Chamillionaire.
The I mean the legacy of this song is
just like it got into the wrong hands.
>> It did, but that's that's actually like
the perfect example of a one hit wonder
where it's like you got a little too
carried away. Like we got it like here's
the thing, you can't play Ridin'
anymore. Like it's like we just like
Oh, we played this into the [__]
When I tell you y'all
dog, I thought I was the man when I was
playing that song. I'm just like I'm the
coolest anyone's ever been. I know every
single word. Chamillionaire is going to
take over. He didn't, but I think he's
in What what's Chamillionaire up to? Is
he into crypto or something?
He's got an NFT. He's He definitely had
an NFT or a coin or something.
>> No, it was like NFTs or something. I was
like damn, go get you. It was It was
Chamillionaire like I think cuz one of
my favorite groups is Pretty Ricky and
like I don't know one day I was just
like I wonder what the members of Pretty
Ricky
Wait, have you ever listened to Pretty
Ricky? No, I don't think so. Baby girl
with me. Relax your mind, take your time
with Wait, what? I just maybe if I heard
it, but that doesn't sound like
>> You wasn't watching 100 or 106 & Park?
We didn't have cable growing up. Damn.
>> Yeah. All right, well, I'm not drafting
Pretty Ricky wonder.
Ridin'. All right, you have to pick.
>> I've got two, okay.
Come on.
All right, I'm going to go
>> You can't let Justin keep getting away
with it. I'm going to go
I'm going to let me get my worst song
out of the way.
I've got two here.
I've got one that will just is going to
be a Charles trigger.
And I have one that probably we all
agree on. Okay.
Do we want to Do I want to get spicy or
not? Get spicy. Here's the thing in my
worst song
>> It might actually get the whole audience
mad cuz I think people really like this
song.
>> pick Shake It Off by Taylor Swift the
worst song, but I'm like we don't need
the negativity. Like I'm just like
that's going to ruin my whole day.
Like I'm just like that's going to ruin
the whole day. I legitimately like that
song, but it has one of the worst
bridges of all time.
>> Of all time of all time, but I'm like
Swifties don't
Hey, y'all going through enough with
that last album. I don't want to I
respect y'all and the girl anyway.
>> like wood?
Okay.
All right, let's just let's just let's
mix it up. I'm going to go worst song of
the 21st century. I'm going Usher's Yeah
with Lil Jon.
This was literally in contention for my
number one song. Same. This was on my
number one song list. This is
>> I hate this song. This is
I'm I'm going to I'm going full Charles
heel turn right now, but I have never
liked this song. This is egregious. Like
I hear it way too much. It's one of the
most overplayed songs at stadiums at any
any You know dude, here cuz this is how
I know you wasn't outside.
When we was watching the video and Usher
throws a chain around and like bro, like
there's like there's Neo in the Matrix
when he was doing the
and there's the chain flipping the hood.
Like I this is actually I'm so mad at
you. This was a cultural moment. This
was an institution. This changed music
forever. How dare you?
>> I'm so sorry.
I'm just going with my heart. I learned
from I've hanging out with you too much.
I'm going with my heart and
>> I thought you were going to do like
Hotline Bling and I'm like okay. And I
and I don't care what the audience
thinks. You don't want to know my number
two though. My runner-up was going to be
Radioactive Imagine Dragons. Dog, this
was in contention.
On my list, too. But here's the thing, I
got a hot take.
I got to [__] RADIOACTIVE.
I GOT TO [__] RADIOACTIVE.
[__] the most Charles thing ever. God
damn, DUDE. WAIT, RADIOACTIVE GOT like
in the whip SOMETIMES I'M LIKE ALL
RIGHT, LET'S PUT a little Imagine
Dragons on. Let's really show them how
we living. Wait, really? Imagine Dragons
actually has some bops. They're
terrible, but they have some The one the
only one Kendrick has one stain on his
career and it's the Imagine Dragons
collaboration.
>> the Bad Blood. Bad Blood remix. Yeah,
that's hot.
I love that song.
>> He He said that's hot.
This is this is the this is some girl
dad [__] and we don't need that. This is
some girl dad [__] cuz you're like
hey
You're like HEY GIRLS, YOU WANT TO
LISTEN TO SOME
JUST WANT TO SAY we're leaving some
really terrible songs.
>> Okay, yeah, let's run through since
everyone got their pick in. So give us
the short list.
>> Okay, here's here's some songs that I
had on my list and this was very
incomplete. My second pick was going to
be Fireflies by Owl City. No, no, no. I
love that song. I love that song.
>> like that song.
Okay, but it's just a Postal Service
rip-off. Okay, it's a Postal It's a
terrible Postal Service rip-off. It's
really bad. It's an AI version of Postal
Service. Here's a song that I I'm pretty
sure that I that Charles is going to say
he loves, but probably deserves being
contention.
Beautiful Girls.
I love it.
All these beautiful
girls They only want to Can I just say
real quick? My one memory of Beautiful
Girls. You want to know how much I love
this song?
They're like I was I forget where my
family was traveling. I was a child and
on the entire trip I would just listen
to Beautiful Girls over and over again
and I thought it was the greatest song
of all time. This is disrespectful.
Anyway, continue Justin. I mean like you
know, we can talk about like
conservative country songs like Try That
in a Small Town or some [__] That
doesn't those are just don't even come
I think Taylor Swift's Me is actually
the one that's a that is a really bad
song.
I had several Eminem songs on this list
and they ranged from Just Lose It
Oh.
Yeah. to
This is going to get me in trouble. Rap
God. Yeah. That was the end.
The Lil Dicky Earth song with everyone
on it.
Lil Dicky No, no. Never mind, I'm
getting too spicy.
You know, we were we were out last night
and behind both of your backs I was
asking people what's the worst song of
the century and there were like
extensive debates about Black Eyed Peas.
No, we're not we're not throwing any
dirt on the Black Eyed Peas. Like they
legends. Like they did too much. Like we
not doing that. Like
let's get it started.
You want to know my take was? Let's Get
It Started
uh got um to Tonight's Going to Be a
Good Night Good Feeling whatever
whatever like My Humps all those songs,
they weren't going to be the Black Eyed
Peas pick for me. Mine was going to be
Where Is the Love?
Ooh, that yeah. Yes, that's
>> Wait, what about I not not I Got a
Feeling?
I No, that that that has that has
soundtracked too many
too many moments of
Come on, you you were like in high
school around that age. You know I [__]
with the Black Eyed Peas. That's heavy.
I had the CDs. I went to Border to cop
that [__]
>> And then the last thing I had on my list
was just anything to Tekashi 69. Oh,
yeah. Oh, yeah. That's that's already I
mean I the one that was probably going
to get me in trouble if I didn't it
wasn't Shake It Off by Taylor Swift.
Would have been Icona Pop. I love it.
Wow. I don't care. I
I was in college when that I literally
wanted to throw my TV. I cannot hear
this song one more time.
This episode is brought to you by Amazon
Prime. The holidays move fast, so stay
in sync with Prime's fast free delivery.
Admittedly, I sometimes wait till the
last minute to buy my gifts and I've
been saved by Prime more than a few
times. That's because Prime's fast
shipping is always there for you during
the holidays, especially when it's last
minute and can't wait. Need that final
gift or holiday essential in a flash?
It's on Prime. Head to amazon.com/prime
to shop now.
All right, now it's my turn. No, I think
I got one more, right?
>> yeah. One more. Okay. So, I went with uh
Sure, yeah.
Um okay, what do I got left? I got
personal favorite.
I've got moment maker and my best and
most important. Okay.
All right, let's go
I'm going to go with my moment maker.
As you took my number one at Runaway,
Justin took my number two at Not Like
Us.
I've been obsessed with Daft Punk
lately. You know this, right? Yes.
>> Both of you guys know this very well.
The song itself
is going to be
Around the World/Harder, Better, Faster,
Stronger mashup
from the Alive 2007
concert series in the pyramid. So, we're
talking moment maker.
One of the most memorable and
influential concert series of all time
is Daft Punk at Coachella.
Revealing the pyramid, one of the best
light show one of the best stage
performances
up until that point in history,
influenced Kanye, influenced everyone
that came after. So, I'm picking
the song itself is arbitrary. I could
have plucked pretty much any song off of
Alive 2007, their live album.
But the moment of the pyramid and that
entire set and everything that came
after, this is coming off the back of
Stronger Kanye sample
and Daft Punk really revitalizing their
career and becoming bigger than ever uh
off the back of their most least popular
album. So, I'm that that is my Does that
my sense? Is it Did I cheat code this a
little bit or
>> I would have just picked Daft Punk, the
pyramid, that entire just like we are
still live that live show. We are still
living in the world that they built.
There are
everything from Yeezus to whatever like
there are artists that are just like,
yeah, just do a worse version of that.
Like I love the Yeezus tour, but like
that's not the best example, but it's
like
you put me on to the live album. It was
something that like I would listen to
here and there, but like
recently I've been playing it and I was
like, oh. Yeah. This is incredible.
incredible. Yeah.
>> We were talking about it if Daft Punk
went on one more tour like if they did
an Oasis [__] like bro. Oh my god. Bro.
We need it. I think we need it and then
the the best thing about them is they
can put the helmets on anytime. They'll
and they they you know, they don't they
don't have the curse of going out with
long gray hair and All right, so is it
is it my turn now?
>> It's your turn, yeah. Woo. You know
what? I got to go with my heart. I'm
going with moment.
There like there has not been a bigger
peak
a more important run in the 21st century
than
Future's mixtape run.
To be there and bear witness
to Monster, Beast Mode, 56 Nights. He
comes out with DS2. March Madness is
going crazy. Don't even mention Throw
Away off. Like it's just it's it's I'm
getting chills. Coding Crazy. Like this
was at a very impressionable time for
me. If anybody's like, damn, what
happened to you? I'm just like went
through a breakup and then Future's
Monster came out and it was never the
same. I was forever changed and it's
just
this moment touches me. You're looking
at me like
>> What's the What's the song though?
Oh, what? So, can Do we do a Do you want
me to pick a song from the mixtape?
>> to have you know, it's technically a
song draft, so just
>> Okay, I'm doing I'm doing I'm doing I'm
doing
>> Harder, Better to represent the moment
with
>> I'm going to do Coding Crazy.
>> Okay. Cuz my favorite my favorite
is Throw Away,
but I think Coding Crazy is the one that
for better or worse when you were
thinking about
what would happen to music
the drug influence
it runs not only through like rap and
SoundCloud rap, but it also starts
infecting pop music as well. So, I'm
think I'm going to go I'm going to go
Coding Crazy and then
everything that would come all the
mixtapes that would come after thanks to
the kind of like the massive success of
that.
Charles? Yes. Okay. We both have a lot
of affection for this run. I had on my
on my favorite song list Coding Crazy
was on that list. It This wasn't on my
moment maker's list, but I it was on my
semi short list
>> Okay.
>> of favorites.
Um
when you started that sentence
I thought you were going to go in a
different direction for best mixtape
run, best best moment that kind of
culminates that of the century. Oh, I I
I had it was it was between two artists.
It was between two mixtape runs. Well,
that's the thing, right? And I'm I've
actually decided just now I'm not going
to pick that. So, like let's debate
this. Who had a better mixtape run?
Future or Lil Wayne?
In my heart
Wayne's rapping
Wayne the way the way Wayne was
attacking beats, the way I felt, the way
it was just like, oh, if Wayne gets on
your song or flips it, it's over. The
fact that Barack Obama was calling him
out A Milli when like when we think like
A Milli was a hit.
>> Right, yeah. It's crazy. No hook, yeah.
But I think a lot of those Wayne songs
also don't necessarily age well. Like
Lil Wayne's mixtape run ages well as a
moment, but Future's mixtape run ages
well as like songs and albums.
I think there's also you see
the DNA of Future all over music still.
Yeah. Honestly, like
a Future knockoff
they might not be good, but can sounds
kind of okay.
>> Yeah. Lil Wayne knockoff Oh my god.
It was one of the worst periods of rap.
But I'll I'll tell you this though,
can I tell you this though?
Isn't it interesting that Lil Wayne's
mixtape run is actually a mixtape run
where Future's mixtape run was just a
bunch of albums where it's like you even
see the difference of just like Wayne's
mixtapes were clas like hosted by DJ
Drama, Gangsta Grillz, The Drought. He's
rapping over over other people's beats.
They're not dropping on DSPs where it's
like with Future, it's like yes,
technically it's a mixtape run,
but all of those are just albums and
some of them had DJs on them. But isn't
that Is that also a product just of the
timing of them in in terms of like the
rise of streaming and then this being
this weird hybrid of like what is a
mixtape, what is an album now that you
can just put it on streaming or is that
Well, I think it was like back then it's
like
Wayne was rapping over other people's
beats and stuff not getting stuff
cleared where it's like we more so I
would burn Wayne mixtapes to play them
in my car or I would still go to DatPiff
where it's like now for a lot of artists
they're just like
if I rap over someone's beat, I could
put it on YouTube, but it just makes
more sense to just make a wholly new
song.
>> Right, yeah.
Did you guys Did you guys answer the
question?
Uh we didn't answer the question. I
can't I can't I can't.
>> Oh, you have to be tiebreaker this time.
Oh, I'm I'm I'm the wrong person to ask.
I'm going to go Lil Wayne cuz I was more
there. The Future stuff happened in my
black hole as we've talked about many
times on this, so I just wasn't there
and then you kind of reintroduced me to
the a lot of that stuff through the
cultural exchanges, but I vividly
remember a lot of the the the Wayne
mixtape stuff. The energy around that
time is insane.
>> it maybe if we're if we're talking
mixtape though, then maybe to your point
about Wayne's being a little bit more
traditional in a mixtape sense, maybe we
give it to Wayne.
You know what though? I've I've actually
just right now in past 10 seconds talked
myself in another direction. Okay.
Wayne obviously carried Cash Money on
his back,
but Future was kind of at the beginning
of the ascent of Atlanta rap just taking
over music cuz like
>> Yeah, yeah. you have Rich Gang, you have
Young Thug, you have Migos, you have uh
you know,
the this this whole second or third wave
depending on how you classify it of
Atlanta artists coming up and just
really took over
what popular music was for a few years
and Future was an enormous part of that.
Yeah.
I'm going I'm going Future. I'm going
Future on that.
>> Oh, yeah. All right, so what was your
Wait, did you make a pick? Wait, where
Where were we last?
>> I picked Coding Crazy. Okay, Coding
Crazy and then now Justin, you're you're
pick. I really got to go to the
bathroom, so I'll let let's let's pause
for a second.
You know what? You just live such a
baller lifestyle. I'm so I'm so jealous.
You know? Some people got all the luck.
I'm I'm I can give you some advice,
Charles. You want
You need some life advice?
I'll set you on the right path. Like
literally? Start like the cameras are
We're rolling with my life advice. We're
taking a break. Justin, and the What
life advice do you have for me?
Have you ever read anything about like
Buddhism or like Taoism? No. Wait. I
think I think that's the I think that's
the the the path I need to put you on.
>> I did read like the
RZA's Wu-Tang like The Tao of Woo or
whatever. And I also No. It's I'm either
getting the Wu-Tang book confused or I
read I think it's called like The Tao of
Pooh. Okay, yeah. It's all It's like
Pooh Bear [__]
>> Right, right, right.
>> know how well that's aged. I I read that
in high school, but like Wait, like are
there any books that you could
recommend? I'm being so serious.
Well, if you want to get like if you
actually I mean Tao Te Ching Have you
ever heard of Tao Te Ching? It's like
the foundational text of Taoism.
It's like all of It's like I forgot how
many short very short um
I don't even know not not called poems,
but
you can read one paragraph essentially
of text and you could just think about
it forever.
But it's all grounded in you know the
way and just kind of I'm texting you.
Okay. Being Being like water, you know?
Path of least resistance, just
breath.
[__] you.
>> You know, center yourself and then
everything blossoms around you. Dog, we
about to get the chillest Charles.
The hate is about to leave. But here's
the thing, the hate leaves my system,
but do people still love me?
See that Okay, see this is This is
getting interesting, actually, cuz I
think there's some truth there.
There's what? I think there's some truth
in that statement. I'm like here's the
thing, I'm I'm I'm the Pusha T of the
rap
game and I'm just like [__] it, let's
go. That's what people come to me for.
So,
I'm never going to be the biggest, but
you know what I'm saying? I'm going to
be negative, though. Three Maybe we need
like a psycho like a
therapy podcast.
Last song standing therapy
therapy quarter.
All right. All right, yo.
Honestly, we had the deepest conver-
This literally this episode's going to
cut. All right, we're back. Justin, we
had a REALLY DEEP CONVERSATION.
ALL RIGHT, you have It's your pick,
Cole. Okay, so Justin, you have two
picks next, right?
>> two picks coming up. I have three picks
left. So, I have just to recap, okay? I
have done
my number one pick, the first pick of
this entire thing, Not Like Us.
I I feel good about it.
>> I
It's just funny. I don't know why it's
funny.
>> song, I picked Grindin' by the Clipse.
Uh my worst song, I picked the just a
truly terrible song. It actually is so
terrible I'm picturing like this pops up
on social media. I'm picturing the song
is just so bad that it might just like
actually put the stink on my entire
list, but it was Rude by Magic. Uh
shoutout white boy, shoutout reggae.
Um
So, that means that I have one hit
wonder
uh moment maker and best
favorite. My one hit wonder
and this is partly inspired by the by my
recent experience viewing the movie One
Battle After Another three times. It's
Shut Up and Dance. No, it's
It's Mo Bamba by Sheck Wes.
But it's a great It is a great song.
That's such a good song.
>> It's a great song. I will be, but it's
very performative male of you. Having
Clipse grinding in 2025, Not Like Us,
and Mo Bamba
is is
It says a lot about you.
>> Who's Who's
Who's got the Who's party you showing up
to?
Honestly
Wait, actually no. Cole's party is
pretty good, actually. Irreplaceable,
Panda, worst song being Usher. Yeah,
that actually really helps. This is
actually
Of all of our lists, yours is the least
scaring the hoes of the list. I know.
Me and Justin I picked a Kanye song
first. I WAS
I GOT HAPPY. ALL MY SONGS ARE CURSED.
YEAH, I got I got the you're a pedophile
song. I got
I got then then immediately I'm going to
marry your daughter. And I'm doing white
boy reggae. This is actually
Yeah, this is actually bad. All right,
okay, but Mo Bamba is a great choice.
>> I actually like
when it's I knew it was going to get One
Battle After Another and I still was
like I know. I know. It's such a
Just imagining PTA listening to Sheck
Wes and being like [__] yeah.
Yo.
If you could get PTA
on this podcast to dissect one film with
him, which film would it be? That's a
good question.
To dissect specifically
Oh.
I mean, There Will Be Blood's my
favorite.
And maybe Yeah.
You don't want a Boogie Nights at this
age? No. I don't need that. Master?
Actually, yeah, The Master. Really?
>> Yeah, I think it would be The Master.
>> it would ruin it. I think it would ruin
the mystery if you know too much about
it. If he says too much about it, I
think it ruins the mystique. There Will
Be Blood does it. You It's Well, what's
the point of doing a dissection with him
then?
>> true, then. This is true. All right, the
right choice, Master?
Yeah, The Master was the one I was
thinking, but it has to be There Will Be
Blood or The Master. I think I think the
I think in terms of like interpreting
the text of the film,
those those would be the most
interesting.
>> Yeah.
Um
>> All right, next next pick?
So
and just real quick
Charles, you Charles, you still have
number one on the board, right?
>> Yep.
And what else do you still have on the
board? You still have favorite. Everyone
still has favorite on the board, right?
>> Everyone still has favorite. I'm going
with my heart with favorite.
>> Yeah, I think I think favorite We're
probably all going to hold off till
last. So
This is So, now I have to go with moment
maker.
I got to make things right with all the
scaring the hoes music.
I got I got a I got to make things
right.
Um
This was an album that we didn't discuss
on the best albums of the 21st century.
Uh run on last song standing.
Uh we discuss the
artist actually ended up winning with a
different album, ended up winning with
Blonde.
But my moment maker
I'm going with Thinking About You by
Frank Ocean.
And that moment when that album first
dropped a couple days after that letter
came out
kind of kind of changed the the tide of
Charles, you're shaking your head.
I see you shaking your
>> It's because it's because it's
egregious. I can tell that Cole and I
are really going with our hearts. And I
can tell that this ain't really your
list. Like you really mapped it out in a
way that is just It's okay. It's okay.
You like But it's
Like Cole, can you can you back me up? I
Well, I mean, I get what you're saying,
but these are all great songs. So, how
do I push back on you on that?
>> but Justin picking them is funny.
Justin pick- Justin picking them is
funny.
>> Why Why is What is funny about me
picking the Clipse?
You not
They got the best album of the year. We
know people activated for the Clipse.
You know what I mean? All I'm saying is
we saw it. It It started Here's the
thing, if you didn't draft Not Like Us
first
I'd give you more sway.
>> Okay, set the tone, yeah.
>> But Thinking About Wait, honestly, I'm
I'm I'm surprised you didn't go off go
with something off Blonde. Thinking
About You is This is This is the right
pick. Really? I think so.
>> I think so. It's the first song on the
album a couple days after that letter
comes out. It kind of
It changed everything.
>> Change everything. Change everything.
You know what It became a meme, which I
think is important to these comp- the
the potato. Potato flew around my room.
You remember that?
>> Yeah, I don't know this, but yeah, I'll
I'll take it for the argument. The The
opening line, the tornado flew around my
room. There's a meme that's like a
potato flew around my You haven't You
haven't heard this?
>> I've never seen this.
>> A potato flew around my room before you
came. Excuse me. Like I like I've never
seen this before. What?
>> Okay, Cole Cole's on the wholesome
internet. I don't Yeah. A potato flew
around my room. That sounds like a a
really fun place to be as opposed to the
cursed part of the computer that I'm
that I'm stuck on.
>> This is early internet, you know.
>> We were we were living two separate
lives at this time. But like I love
Thinking About You. I'm not going to
sing it, but honestly
guys don't pick Thinking About You at
karaoke, I realized.
Um The falsetto is
>> is rough. It's rough. What's your go-to
karaoke song?
It's Ne-Yo. Recently, it's been So Sick.
It's I've been in the So Sick Ne-Yo.
>> Okay. Have you ever heard So Sick?
Yeah. Not in like a over a decade,
probably.
>> Uh but I have some others. We've been
over this. So Sick by Ne-Yo, I've
retired and I'm Numb / Encore by Jay-Z
and Linkin Park. Um I am doing uh
1, 2 Step by Ciara now. Missy Elliott
rap. Really [__] with it. It's like
I I could do some karaoke. I bet you
could. I can't sing, but like
I can get the crowd involved. I can get
us moving. So, I got some Follow Up Boy
songs. Killer, Dance Dance, and
Oh, I forgot about Follow Up All right,
let me I'm not spoiling anything. I'm
not Okay.
That was your two. Charles, you're next.
It's me?
Ooh. So, you have your personal favorite
and you have I got number one. Hm.
You know what? I got to go. I got to go
with my heart.
I got to go with 50 Cent's In Da Club.
Like In Da Club, like people are like
I'm like, guys, you don't actually
realize
how massive of a moment this is.
>> That was That was in my short list for
even moment maker. Really? Because it
was Come on. Every G Unit, every I've
never
I
I'm young. I'm young, but in my
lifetime, I've never seen a rapper
come out like that and literally every
song they touch is a hit. People wear G
Unit [__] The video was on constantly.
Yeah. My parents like the song. Like you
know like my middle-aged parents were
like In Da Club is one of them joints. I
had the the G-Unit DVD that you could
you could buy.
Did you How much G-Unit I didn't I wear
I didn't wear the [__] I had What?
>> a much
I'm
suburban skinny white kid.
>> If I got you some G-Unit If I got you
some vintage G-Unit next time we we do
Last Song Standing, would you wear some?
No. What Really? Did you wear Rocawear?
No. I
I had Rocawear and G-Unit No, no, no. I
didn't I didn't have either of those. I
had the Wait, what? I was By that point
I was wearing Ecko. I was I was that
kind of head. I had some You had some
Ecko.
No. I See, I think I would like to say I
had like enough sense back then even
back then that I I didn't try to do the
I've never tried to do like the hip-hop
look.
As much as I like hip-hop, I was just
never that guy. I never really tried to
pretend to be that guy.
We going to get you some LRG.
some Ecko we We'll get some FUBU. FUBU
FUBU Karl Kani What is bringing it way
back? The S. Carters
Like
>> liked it. I always I mean I always
thought it looked cool.
>> the cipher complete.
Like Cole Cole
I'm a I know
I know the Christmas gift. We we got
some for you. Okay. Come on. All right,
yo. This is your last two picks.
>> Last two picks. I still have my best
best most important song and personal
favorite. So
We didn't make it a formal rule, but we
were kind of you know, we're trying to
avoid overlap.
There's just not There's no way I I
can't pick either Frank Ocean or for and
Kendrick in this category in my most
important best song.
I just I I got it I'm going to just
cheat the rules a little bit. We've
talked a lot about Self Control on this
podcast.
>> Yeah.
I'm not sure if that in a best or most
important song
I guess you can make the case that
Blonde is the best album of the century
and so you're picking something off of
that.
Not Like Us was on my short list for
best most important
but I think it's not my favorite
Kendrick song, but in this category
specifically
I think I have to land on Kendrick
Lamar's All Right.
It's a cliché pick. I'm sorry. I'm
sorry.
>> It had to be picked. It's I'm sorry, but
yes, it had to be even mad about it.
Like I was like someone has to pick it.
We've We've talked enough about it on
this podcast. We all understand it comes
off one of the best albums of the
century.
It was chanted in the streets. It
represents a cultural moment and you can
you can have a conversation about this
century through the song. What's your
actual Kendrick pick though? If it if
it's like if we're just like going with
your heart.
In this In this category or like In this
category.
I think it would have to be
It'd have to be Sing About Me probably.
But I I get why.
>> Yeah, it's like
>> fit the mold.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah. All right, no. Yeah,
all right. Here's the thing. I actually
thought
it was going to be picked in moment.
It was on my short list. There's a lot
of overlap between
any Kendrick song you're going to have
it's going to have that The Moment too
cuz it was All Right at the Grammys was
also a moment short list for me.
But that ties into why it's one of the
best and most important too. So I'll go
All Right.
Sorry for the cliché pick. It had to be
done. And then personal pick? Personal
pick This is the one I actually had the
most trouble with because I have so many
favorite songs of mine.
I've talked a lot about Radiohead on
this podcast. Yep. And I didn't want to
overlap too much. We've talked about
Everything in Its Right Place in this
same series. We talked about How to
Disappear Completely off of Kid A in
this series in our in our Last Song
Standing series.
There's one song we didn't talk about
not on our Radiohead project
on a Justice project. A an album that
was close to being considered a an
episode for Last Song Standing.
Genesis by Justice
If I'm going If I'm going
>> [__] Wow. Incredible pick. Incredible
pick.
You know if I was trying to be
technical, it'd be a Radiohead song. I'm
trying to mix it up. So I'm going to go
just Genesis Justice. This song I get
This is 2007.
I talked about how this was a formative
time in my life. This album specifically
came at a time when I was getting
interested in classical music.
They sample a Brahms symphony and turn
it into one of the most grimy, dark
just when I put Genesis on
it's like the opposite of Everything in
Its Right Place in terms of
that song will touch my heart. There's
something about Genesis that
gets in my blood. And just
there's it just
I You like this song, Charles? Not only
do I love this song, I'm jealous that I
didn't. Like I'm Now I'm like why the
[__] didn't I do this? Cuz I When I tell
you I still listen to this album like
>> Yeah. Oh, yeah. multiple times like in a
month I'll just be like I'll be riding
around in the whip and I'll put Genesis
is an inspired And like I've been
getting into like some other Justice
albums recently like
>> Their newest one I returned to it. Their
newest one is actually really good.
Dog.
Last song standing Justice
Charles, how do you feel about this
choice? I think this is inspired and I
think that uh
I really appreciate you going with your
heart and not trying to win a draft.
But no, but
it's a it's a great pick. I told you I'm
not competitive.
>> great album. That whole
that whole
album that whole scene is also a moment
in a way, right? Yeah. I remember seeing
the Genesis tour where they had the
[__]
Marshall all those Marshall guitar amp
speakers. Do you guys remember this? It
was just a wall
>> Yep. [__] so high of of Marshall They
didn't use them. It was just for
aesthetic. Cuz they're tapping into the
rockstar thing. They'd come out in their
their leather jackets looking just
[__] so cool.
And I wanted to be them. And yeah, they
defined like that second wave of French
EDM or I guess a French electro.
The whole Ed Banger thing. I just
imagine American Apparel V-necks.
You know what I mean? That whole scene.
Were you too young to to be into the
into that? Were you dressing that way
back then 2007?
>> Yeah, the deep the deep V's. Come on. I
was from the Jersey Shore. V-necks hit
that [__] crazy.
I thought I was the I was in my V-necks.
I thought I was the man. That [__] looks
terrible now.
I'm like [__]
>> you guys Okay, you guys were talking
about like hip-hop clothing. My
embarrassing photos are like the V-necks
and the tight jeans.
Oh, wow. Yeah, that was
Also the skinny jeans and the V-necks
were nasty, weren't they? It's nasty.
>> It was It's nasty. I look back on it and
I'm like what were we thinking? It was
so nasty.
Okay, I think I'm done. So Charles, back
to you for your final pick. You guys
already know what my personal pick is
going to be.
Usher?
Confessions?
I'mma keep turning it in and turn
it into the same genre. I want you want
to go.
When I was a kid, there were a couple
musicians and there were like that I
would like wait on BET to watch.
And Confessions Part II I thought was
one of the deepest. Just to quirk some
of the times I was like how can a man
be this vulnerable about his pain and
and what he did to the woman of his
life. You guys know I'm a romantic.
What Usher
slides
AND ROCKS THE WOMAN.
I WAS like yo.
This is the greatest thing of all time.
I can't believe two Usher songs made it
on the 20 worst One best song and one
worst song.
>> I had to. I had to clean it up. Okay.
Guys, Confessions Part II I'm sorry. I'm
bringing it up every
single season. It is You want to know
All right. Confessions Part II y'all
know that's a Charles pick. You want to
know what else?
If we had a best verse Like I like Okay.
I would pick for this. That'd be a good
category. I wanted 50 Cent's opening uh
verse on uh Hated or Loved It. Mhm. I
almost wanted to pick Hated or Loved It
in this cuz like every couple months
I'll be like damn Hated or Loved It is a
great song.
Growing up always confused my mama
KISSING A GIRL.
LIKE HE WAS GIVING us his soul.
Justin, you can call me uh
It's a no?
No. I I just it's
This feels better about you know, we
didn't have the rule, but like the the
informal unspoken rule of two artists.
Like worst and best feels right.
Uh
This is me talking all night friendship.
I know. This is a really perfect
encapsulation right here.
All right, yo. Justin, I think it's it's
you. You have
one more pick or two more? I have one
more. All right.
>> And it's it's personal.
This was the category I struggled with
the most.
>> Yeah. Because
a lot of my personal songs I think just
wouldn't even like scan on this list.
Like Modest Mouse is my favorite band,
but like their only song that was really
enormous was Float On and that wouldn't
be my song. Modest Mouse is your
favorite band? How did I never know
this? Yeah, but like I'm I'm into the
early
But like
it's I can't pick something like that or
like you know, I I can just
>> pick whatever you want. You are putting
rules on yourself. I can, but this is
also a product that people are going to
consume at some point. You start talking
about [__] they don't know about. It's
the end of the pod, man.
>> end of the pod, bro. It's a personal
pick. You're already going to win.
>> And he might And he might turn someone
on to their next favorite song.
>> Well, if the people should go listen to
Modest Mouse Moon & Antarctica.
Uh it as for an album. They should do
that. I'm not going to pick that. They
should also go listen to Songs of Ahaya.
I was going to pick maybe Farewell
Transmission or that song. I I keep a
little playlist called my funeral
playlist  incomplete.
>> Jesus Christ.
It's incomplete. It's incomplete. Uh
these songs are on it. It's basically my
my girlfriend knows that if something
were to happen to me, this has to play.
Okay. Um
I struggled with
what I wanted to do. There were there
were some songs that I was deciding
between. I think I feel like I There was
part of me that wanted to make it right
for the Jay-Z versus Beyoncé episode and
go with my heart on that and pick like
Heart of the City to just do apologies
for.
>> Uh that's a That'd be great.
>> That would be great.
That'd be a great choice. There's a big
part of me that wanted to go I'm going
to go with my heart on this one. This is
going to feel weird to land it, but this
is I I really wanted to go with
D'Angelo. Voodoo is one of my favorite
albums of the
20 21st century is one of this is
like the first album of the 20 21st
century, too, but RIP D'Angelo. What I
struggled with there is the song I
really would have wanted to go with
there was Devil's Pie, but that didn't
feel right. Like I would have had to go
with Untitled. That kind of felt like
more pandering. I am going to go with my
heart and I'm sorry. I'm going with
Jadakiss and Styles P We Gonna Make It
produced by The Alchemist.
It's a song that has just lived with me
for almost 25 years now.
I'm sorry. Might be the most obscure
pick on this, but after all
>> I actually think it's like
it's the best pick. It's like it's the
best pick. Jadakiss back
everything that happened at the Dipset
versus. Like [__] When I finally When I
finally landed the same I was like [__]
he did it.
It has the best opening line of any rap
song of the century. [__] the frail
[__]
Cuz what happens?
Cuz when my coke come in, they're going
to use the scale that they weigh the
whales with.
>> Yes. Sorry. My
It's been a week. My We should cut that
out. I I know the follow-up to that, but
this inspired. [__]
>> After all the pandering. I love it. It's
It's a such a Justin choice.
>> It's such a Justin See, this is what I
wanted the entire episode from him. To
just go with his heart. They had to go
from Not Like Us to We Gotta Make It.
It's pretty That's an arc. It's an arc.
All right. Do we want to read our Do we
want to read our
uh Well, actually before we do that, the
the funeral music's got my mind
thinking.
Do you Do you have a funeral song?
Can you Is there one that you would Do
you know what I mean? Shout out Shout
out to Woz. They were talking about this
on Group Chat.
I don't really [__] with thinking about
my funeral like that. Like I feel like
if I think about what I want to play at
my funeral is bad vibes. You know what I
mean? Like at that point like
If I know it's coming, I'm a I'm going
to throw some [__] together. But it's
like if you want to But
This is actually bring
Is it just Usher's Confessions? Just
play the whole album. No, cuz the real
thing is like I have to warn people when
they get in my car sometimes. I'm just
like all right, I'm going to play
annoying music and they're just like
what do you mean?
I'm going to listen to like bibbity boop
like hyperpop [__] Like 100 gecs. Like
I kid you not. Like I'm listening to
like [__] where people
The first time Van and the Midnight Boys
got into my car, Van goes
Oh, this is the [__] you listen
So, it would be like annoying hyperpop
[__] and people would be like turn this
off. We're glad he's gone.
Wait, so what would yours be?
I haven't thought about this in forever,
but
for a long time it was Everything in its
in its right place Radiohead.
I just like the symbology of Everything
in Its Right Place cuz you know
>> That's beautiful. If you asked me as a
kid, it would be I Believe I Can Fly by
R. Kelly. It would no longer be that
for obvious reasons. We're We're We're
at the two R. Kelly references on this
episode.
He loomed very large and and
thankfully he is behind bars where he
belongs. It's It's weird hearing my
daughters sing that song cuz
>> Wait, they know I Believe I Can Fly?
Space Jam.
They like the original Space Jam Wait,
for real? Yeah. More than the LeBron
version. Here's And what's also crazy
they definitely had us singing I Believe
I Can Fly at like kindergarten
graduation. Like it was For sure.
Honestly, there
That was bad. So, I was Wait. Actually,
this is a good I haven't I've never
thought about this. It Actually, I think
I would do something beautiful, you
know? Like I think I would I would pick
like a Whoo Whoo. I'll probably pick
like a Toni Braxton song. Something real
like You don't want Okay, see my
thinking is like you want to make the
people there feel okay. Yeah.
You want to make You don't want to make
them more sad. You want to make them
feel like it's all it's all good.
Uh what's the Toni Braxton song I like I
Get So High When I'm Around You, Baby. I
just like get them like moving.
>> Do you know what that song's about?
I No. What's Sex?
Orgasming? It's a It's about those
things,
but not with another person, Charles.
Oh.
With the with drugs?
No.
>> No, Charles. I'll I'll tell you how I'll
tell you how things work off the air.
Solo like solo work, right? Oh,
masturbation?
>> Yeah. Yes. Oh, okay. Damn. You can just
tell Here's the thing also.
>> It's a family podcast.
Here's the thing.
If people want to come to my funeral and
celebrate my life, they have to
celebrate it on my terms.
[__] it. So, you're you're good with the
masturbation symbology. Yeah. Toni
Braxton. That's That's my choice for
now. It might change. Okay. All right.
Um Well, I have a 100 song playlist. Oh
my god.
This explains so much
Um about you, Justin.
>> But the the song would be uh Talking
Heads This Must Be the Place the live
version. Okay. The live version
specifically from the movie Stop Making
Sense. Mhm.
Are you going to haunt your guest if
they don't play the live version?
They can't You can't not the studio
version's great. Studio version's an
all-timer. The the live version might be
like my favorite thing that's ever been
recorded.
Okay. How are we How are we feeling? How
do we How did we do? I think well, let's
let's do a recap. Justin, you got the
list? I do. Okay. Um this is a little
bit out of order. So,
Cole, you had your number one song
number one hit was Irreplaceable by by
Beyoncé. Your one-hit wonder was Panda
Desiigner. Hell yeah. Your worst song
was Yeah by Usher.
Uh disrespecting Usher Ludacris
and Lil Jon.
>> I'm sorry. That's crazy work.
>> I'm sorry. Uh he
used to Pharrell a good continue.
>> Yeah. Moment Maker.
Around the World  Better, Faster,
Harder, Stronger. Did I get those words
in the right order? Probably not. It's
fine. Okay. Um from the Pyramid Tour
Alive the the Daft Punk live
album.
Your best moment
best Sorry. Your best song was All Right
by Kendrick Lamar. Your personal choice
was Genesis by Justice.
Charles.
>> Love it.
Your best song
Runaway. Yep.
>> Kanye West.
Your worst song Happy by Pharrell.
>> Happy by Pharrell. Your one-hit wonder
Ride It.
It's a good one.
>> Your moment the Future mixtape run
culminating in Codeine Crazy last song
off Monster. Great song. Number one song
number one hit was In Da Club.
Your personal favorite was Confessions
by Usher. Part two. Hell yeah. Part two.
Sorry.
>> All right. And then what
This list is going to piss me off.
Number one Not Like Us.
That's my number one number one hit.
Best song Grindin' by The Clipse. Worst
song
Rude.
One-hit wonder Mo Bamba.
Moment Maker Thinking About You Frank
Ocean.
Personal choice We Gonna Make It by
Jadakiss and Styles P.
This is closer than I expected,
actually.
Well, in terms of a winner? Yeah.
I mean
This is closer than I expected.
>> winning mean?
This is such a Cole You're just like we
just were so competitive. You're like
but That's the That's the religion you
were just talking about Tao. Yeah,
Taoism. Taoism? Yeah. It's not about
It's not about who wins. It's about the
the bond that we just created in this
90-minute podcast.
>> Man, [__] all that [__] I'm trying to
win. I'll be so honest. That's why You
are right. We are going to have We are
going to have a section a therapy
section with you because I am too
concerned with winning. We did just have
a bond, but if I like won
and we created the bond, isn't that
better? What do they say about that in
your religion?
If you created a bond and you won? Yeah.
Those are competing ideas.
Ah, [__] Cuz a winner inherently if
someone wins, then someone else loses.
What And now you're just going, you
know, hierarchy, patriarchy, power,
manipulation. You know what I mean?
Amongst friends? Amongst
you know? [__] you right. We bonded.
Man. Okay, but if I mean if we're
thinking consensus, Justin won.
I don't think so. I mean you kind of
spoiled with the last pick, Justin. I
know. I know.
>> Which was a last-minute pivot I think we
talked you into. I don't think that was
your original pick. No, I the the
Kayla, our wonderful engineer over here.
You can see that I had three songs on my
favorite, and the number one was the one
I went with.
>> Okay.
>> with That was the first song I jotted
down. Okay. Almost went with Dipset
Anthem. I almost went with Cam'ron. I
thought you were going with Cam'ron for
sure.
>> I thought you were going with Cam'ron. I
literally I would have done They Ready
if I was doing my Dipset song.
>> done They Ready?
Uh
Are you guys proud
>> that I didn't pick a Radiohead song?
Yeah. I'm honestly, I'm proud how how
long you waited out for Kendrick. Like
you really waited. What? What songs did
we not discuss? Cuz I have a couple here
like for best song and
B.o.B. B.o.B. Yeah, that's yeah. I
almost Miss Jackson was also on my short
list for number one.
>> was my number two number one choice.
Uh
Uh well, I Someone Like You, Adele,
number one.
>> Adele was on my list.
>> Yeah.
Rolling in the Deep was on my list.
>> Yeah. That's my Adele joint.
>> Okay, yeah. Um great Lil Wayne freestyle
as well over that. Um Mr. Brightside
didn't get picked.
>> Mr. Bright It was on my short list.
[__] Yeah. It was on Wait, did you No
follow-up boy songs?
>> Did that go number one?
>> It did not. Yeah, okay.
>> It didn't?
>> No. Mr. Brightside didn't go number one?
>> You would have had to go and either you
would have had to like invent a moment
and been like, "I'm a big Buffalo Bills
fan and they play that in the stadium."
or something.
Uh
Black and Yellow. Black and Yellow. I
think that's fine. I think that's fine.
Sorry. Um See You Again, also by Wiz
Khalifa. Yeah, see That was almost on my
worst song list to be What?
>> Yeah. No, sorry.
>> That song makes me cry. I love that
song. That's crazy. Shout out Shout out
Paul Walker.
>> Yeah, Day 'n' Night Kid Cudi. No,
honestly
the Day 'n' Night Crooker's remix might
have been in my worst song. Do you
remember that? The what remix? The Day
'n' Night Crooker's remix.
Justin knows exactly
>> I know I know exactly that song. Um yes,
we would When we were playing for normie
crowds when DJing, you you do like
something like that into like the
the the the Heads Will Roll A-Trak remix
from years ago.
>> Speaking of Yeah Yeah Yeahs, Maps was
>> Yeah, Maps for sure. was on my best song
short list.
>> No Drake songs. Are you guys proud of
me? Extremely. Oh yeah, yeah, we didn't
talk about Drake. I almost I almost
bookended the whole thing.
Uh this was also on my list. I almost
bookended by going Story of Adidon. All
right.
Uh
Number one, we didn't No Kill Bill.
SZA. Yeah. Um That was never going to
get picked. My my dad my daughter being
a dad
a daughter-dad Drivers License, Olivia
Rodrigo.
>> Okay. Ooh.
>> That's nice. That's
>> Yeah. sweet.
>> at a lot of Beyoncé Destiny's Child,
Single Ladies, Say My Name. Oh Oh my
I did think of Destiny's Oh my god,
Destiny's Say My That's actually maybe
better than any song any of us picked.
Like I'm just being honest.
Like
Um
>> Do you think Okay, here was an
interesting question.
Is Bad Habit going to be a one-hit
wonder, Steve Lacy?
I don't know. I think that's
>> like a TikTok
That's just That's a different thing to
me. Steve Lacy is like an actual artist
who was not trying to make a hit, and he
just made something that was so
infectious. Yeah. Like I don't consider
him a one-hit Does that make sense?
Yeah. Yeah, you're right. That's right.
>> wonder to me says that they're kind of
still eating off of this one song.
>> Right.
>> Right? Like Billy Ray Cyrus, Achy Breaky
Heart way back. Well, that was a one-hit
wonder. Like that dude's whole life
before his daughter blew up was Achy
Breaky Heart. Uh
Steve Lacy's had a whole career and put
out really good albums. He's not a
one-hit wonder. He just had a song that
blew up.
>> Yeah. Um
Other songs that weren't picked.
Um International Players Anthem. I was
never going to pick it. That's a good
Yeah. I love that song, but pandering. I
agree I agree, even though I couldn't
even go there. Um
What else? Did we miss anything else? I
think we got the big ones.
>> One-hit wonder, I had like Latch by
Disclosure on my long list. Um Yeah.
>> I almost went Crazy by Gnarls Barkley,
but I was like that's a little cheating
because CeeLo and Big Boi have both had
such big careers outside of Gnarls
Barkley.
>> have picked that as a one-hit wonder.
>> Cuz Gnarls Barkley had other hits. That
Yeah. Not bad. Never to that degree, but
>> Never Yeah. It wasn't a Yeah.
Uh
>> You didn't pick No one picked a Jay-Z
song. No Jay-Z song.
>> Uh one-hit wonder, no one picked uh
Somebody That I Used to Know.
Somebody That I Used to Know. I love
that song, too.
Yeah, I guess Yeah, that's a classic
one-hit wonder. Charles, I really almost
I I almost went with my heart in one-hit
wonder and picked Gucci Gucci.
All right, let's wrap it up.
Like let's wrap it up. Shout out Rae
Sremmurd. Shout out Rae Sremmurd, but
come on. Come on. And then
Let's ask the listeners Last Song
Standing. Next season's going to be in
the summer, but if you start thinking
about the artists that you want us to
hit, hit us up on social media. We're
taking suggestions. We are taking We
have someone in mind for the next season
of Last Song Standing, but it's not set
in stone. We have someone in mind, but I
will just tell the listeners.
He going through a lot right now.
He going through a lot right now. You
know what I'm saying? He might He might
need a Last Song Standing season,
to cover some [__]
It's not R. Kelly. It is not R. Kelly.
All right, let's wrap it up.
All right.
All right, y'all.